const contest_40_3 = [
    {
        "S/N": 1,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Saponification is an industrial, alkaline hydrolysis of natural esters.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$\\mathrm{T}$",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry",
        "Topic Tag": ["Saponification", "Organic Chemistry"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 2,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Saponification with caustic soda gives soft soap.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "F.",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry",
        "Topic Tag": ["Saponification", "Organic Chemistry"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 3,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Saponification takes place in the process of digestion of vegetable oils in the gut of humans.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "F.",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry",
        "Topic Tag": ["Saponification", "Organic Chemistry"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 4,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Cyclopentane and 3-methyl-1-butene are isomers.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "T.",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry",
        "Topic Tag": ["Isomerism", "Organic Chemistry"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 5,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "$\\mathrm{Ca}^{2+}$ ions in solution do not form an insoluble sulphide when $\\mathrm{H}_{2} \\mathrm{~S}$ is bubbled through the solution.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "T.",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry",
        "Topic Tag": ["Solubility", "Inorganic Chemistry"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 6,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "The first ionization energy of phosphorus is larger than that of nitrogen.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "F.",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry",
        "Topic Tag": ["Ionization Energy", "Periodic Trends"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 7,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "For the logarithm of a positive number,",
        "Question": "the mantissa is positive,",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "TRUE",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Mathematics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Logarithms", "Mathematics"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 8,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "For the logarithm of a positive number,",
        "Question": "the characteristic is positive",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "FALSE",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Mathematics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Logarithms", "Mathematics"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 9,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "For the logarithm of a positive number,",
        "Question": "the mantissa is itself a logarithm.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "TRUE",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Mathematics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Logarithms", "Mathematics"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 10,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Let functions $\\mathrm{f}$ and $\\mathrm{g}$ have domains $\\mathrm{A}$ and $\\mathrm{B}$ respectively.",
        "Question": "The function $(\\mathrm{f}+\\mathrm{g})(\\mathrm{x})=\\mathrm{f}(\\mathrm{x})+\\mathrm{g}(\\mathrm{x})$ has domain $\\mathrm{A} \\cup \\mathrm{B}$",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "FALSE",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Mathematics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Functions", "Mathematics"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 11,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Let functions $\\mathrm{f}$ and $\\mathrm{g}$ have domains $\\mathrm{A}$ and $\\mathrm{B}$ respectively.",
        "Question": "The composite function $\\mathrm{f}(\\mathrm{g}(\\mathrm{x}))$ has domain $A \\cup B$.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "FALSE",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Mathematics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Functions", "Mathematics"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 12,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Let functions $\\mathrm{f}$ and $\\mathrm{g}$ have domains $\\mathrm{A}$ and $\\mathrm{B}$ respectively.",
        "Question": "The quotient function $\\mathrm{f}(\\mathrm{x}) / \\mathrm{g}(\\mathrm{x})$ has domain $\\mathrm{A} \\cap \\mathrm{B}$.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "FALSE",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Mathematics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Functions", "Mathematics"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 13,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "A charge $q$ outside a grounded conducting sphere at a distance $a$ from the center of the sphere which has a radius $R$ induces a total charge of $-q R / a$ on the sphere.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "True",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Physics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Electrostatics", "Physics"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 14,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "A charge $q$ inside a hollow grounded conducting sphere at a distance $a$ from the center of the sphere which has an inside radius $R$ induces a total charge of $-q R / a$ on the inside surface of the sphere.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "False",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Physics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Electrostatics", "Physics"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 15,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "A charge $q$ inside a hollow grounded conducting sphere cannot induce any charge on the inside surface of the sphere because all charge on a conductor reside on the outside surface of the conductor.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "False",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Physics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Electrostatics", "Physics"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 16,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "The neutron is composed of one up and two down quarks and undergoes beta decay in which a proton is produced.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "True",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Physics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Particle Physics", "Physics"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 17,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "In the beta decay of a neutron, a down quark becomes an up quark with the release of an electron and an electron antineutrino, with the result that a proton is produced.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "True",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Physics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Particle Physics", "Physics"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 18,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "The proton, which is composed of one down and two up quarks, is unconditionally stable because an up quark cannot transform into a down quark.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "False",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Physics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Particle Physics", "Physics"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 19,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Competitive inhibition is seen when a substrate competes with an enzyme for binding to an inhibitor protein",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "False",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology",
        "Topic Tag": ["Enzyme Inhibition", "Biochemistry"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 20,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Non-competitive inhibition of an enzyme can be overcome by adding large amount of substrate",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "False",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology",
        "Topic Tag": ["Enzyme Inhibition", "Biochemistry"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 21,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Competitive inhibition is seen when the substrate and the inhibitor compete for the active site on the enzyme",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "True.",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology",
        "Topic Tag": ["Enzyme Inhibition", "Biochemistry"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 22,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Pedigree analysis confirms that DNA is the carrier of genetic information",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "False",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology",
        "Topic Tag": ["Genetics", "Biology"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 23,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Pedigree analysis helps to understand whether the trait in question is dominant or recessive",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "True",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology",
        "Topic Tag": ["Genetics", "Biology"]

    },
    {
        "S/N": 24,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Pedigree analysis helps to trace the inheritance of a specific trait",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "True",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology",
        "Topic Tag": ["Genetics", "Biology"]

    }
]

export default contest_40_3